* Search for:  

Search for:  

Privacy Policy
==============

Last updated 12/11/2024

**Who are we?**
---------------

We are Chequered Ink Ltd, a limited company based in the United Kingdom. Our registered company number is 09646754 in England & Wales. Our mailing address is Unit 11, 14 Lansdown Mews, Bath, BA1 5DY. Our website is https://chequered.ink and our email address is support@chequered.ink.

**What personal data we collect and why we collect it**
-------------------------------------------------------

When you write to us via post or email, any personal information you send such as your contact details will be stored in order to help you with your query. This information will only be kept for as long as needed to help you and then it will be deleted. We will never use this information for any purpose other than helping with your query.

We collect information about you during the checkout process on our store, and we also have access to the information you provide to itch.io when you purchase our products from there. This information is collected to fulfil orders and for legal and administrative purposes only.

While you visit our site, we’ll track:

* Products you’ve viewed: we’ll use this to, for example, show you products you’ve recently viewed
* Location, IP address and browser type: we’ll use this for purposes like estimating taxes and shipping
* Shipping address: we’ll ask you to enter this so we can, for instance, estimate shipping before you place an order, and send you the order!

Cookies
-------

If you visit the login page, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.

When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.

We’ll also use cookies to keep track of shopping cart contents while you’re browsing our site.

**Local Storage**
-----------------

We use your browser’s local storage to save your progress in our HTML5 games. You can delete local storage data at any time from your web browser’s settings menu.

**Embedded content from other websites**
----------------------------------------

Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.

These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracking your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.

**Who we share your data with**
-------------------------------

If you request a password reset, your IP address will be included in the reset email.

We share information with third parties who help us provide our orders and store services to you; for example our payment providers to whom you provide your card details to make purchases, and our shipping providers if we need to provide your name and address to ship physical products.

**How long we retain your data**
--------------------------------

For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.

Data collected when you email us is stored only as long as it takes for us to deal with your query.

Local storage information is stored locally in your browser, and you can delete this at any time in your browser’s settings.

**What rights you have over your data**
---------------------------------------

If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.

**How we protect your data**
----------------------------

Data you provide when you contact us directly is sent to our secure email server. We regularly perform security checks on our website to minimise the chance of security breaches. Your data is deleted as soon as it is no longer required. Local storage information is stored on your device, not on our servers.

**What data breach procedures we have in place**
------------------------------------------------

We regularly check for breaches to the security of our website. Should any breach become apparent we will immediately act to prevent further damage by securing our servers and we will inform all users that there has been a breach – even if their data wasn’t specifically affected. We will do this via email (if we have a user’s email on file) and by public announcement.

**What automated decision making and/or profiling we do with user data**
------------------------------------------------------------------------

We do not use customer data to profile our users.

**Still worried?**
------------------

If you have any further questions or comments about the privacy policy, please [get in touch](page:86F53D6E-5325-4D54-9C2B-D1D3F8BEEBF6). We’re happy to answer any questions you have.

Chequered Ink © 2015-2024. All Rights Reserved.
